energyatanyage.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Statement for Gundry MD Supplements and Skincare Products

#### SECTION 1 – INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Information Provided by You: We may collect personal information that you provide to us. “Personal information” is information that can be used to identify you individually, and includes items such as your name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number, demographic information, and/or payment information, such as your account or card number, if used to make a purchase from our website. The type of personal information that we may collect depends on your use of this website and what information you provide to us.

#### SECTION 2 – USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION

We use the information that we collect about you for a variety reasons, including the following:

• Verifying your identity;  
• Fulfilling your product orders;  
• Responding to your questions;  
• Providing you with access to certain areas and features of this website;  
• Communicating with you about your purchases and activities on this website;  
• Marketing campaigns to market products and services to you (unless you have opted-out);  
• Adapting content, advertisements, and offers we provide to you directly or through third-party partners;  
• Improving the Website and our customers’ experience; and  
• Sending notices or information.

We may share your personal information with our parent entities, subsidiaries and affiliates for internal reasons, primarily for business and operational purposes. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not share any of your personal information with third parties without your specific consent. We may share non-personal information, such as user statistics or demographics, as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We also contract with certain vendors to assist us in providing services to our customers. These vendors use the Personal Information that you submit to us in order to perform the following tasks:

• Order processing at checkout;  
• Credit card authorization and identity verification;  
• Order shipping and handling;  
• Emailing newsletters and other promotional materials for customers on our mailing list;  
• Storing and “backing up” our customer records.

Finally, notwithstanding the foregoing, we may transfer and disclose information, including your personal information, usage information, and identifying information, including IP address, to third parties to comply with a legal obligation; at the request of governmental authorities; or otherwise to protect the rights, property, safety, or security of third parties, users of this Website, or the public.

#### SECTION 3 – DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

#### SECTION 4 – E-COMMERCE

Our store is hosted on https://gundrymd.com/. Providing you with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.

Your data is stored through https://gundrymd.com/ data storage, databases and the general e-commerce application. We store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

Payment:

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then https://gundrymd.com/ stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

#### SECTION 5 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our website policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

Our store’s payment gateway is hosted by 1ShoppingCart.com. 1ShoppingCart.com has access to aggregate data about our customers in order to assist 1ShoppingCart.com in analyzing Site performance and making improvements to 1ShoppingCart.com products.

In addition, all orders are processed through Network Merchants, LLC. The personally identifiable information Network Merchants, LLC acquires in processing payment transactions varies according to the nature of the transaction and the way in which merchants or financial institutions are using their payment services. It may include, for example, the amount of the transaction, the consumer’s name, credit card number and expiration date, checking account number, billing address, and shipping address.

Network Merchants, LLC uses the information collected to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to process payment transactions, to facilitate billing, and otherwise deliver the payment gateway services. Personal consumer information is used to process payment transactions and for no other purpose.

Network Merchants, LLC stores transaction information on secure computers located in a locked data center. Only a small number of employees involved in the management of the data center have physical access to these computers. Where possible, Network Merchants, LLC encrypts information stored on their computers as a further measure of protection. Network Merchants, LLC uses state-of-the-art firewalls and other security technology to prevent their computers from being accessed by unauthorized persons. Information security is critical to our business. Nevertheless, nothing can be 100% secure. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

Links:

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

#### SECTION 6 – SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

#### SECTION 7 – AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

#### SECTION 8 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

#### SECTION 9 – CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

Many browsers have a “Do Not Track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These browser features are not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to those signals.

Individuals who reside in California and have provided their personal information may request information regarding disclosures of this information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests may be submitted to us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#34474144445b46407453415a50464d59501a575b59) or at the following mailing address: Gundry MD™; Re: Privacy Compliance Officer; 9465 Wilshire Boulevard, Suite 300; Beverly Hills, CA, 90212, United States.

Please outline in your letter or email that you are making a “California Shine the Light” inquiry. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days.

#### SECTION 10 – CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

This Website is not directed to children under the age of thirteen (13) and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen on the Website. Children may not use our services. We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who visit our Website. If a child has provided us with personal information, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities.

#### QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#5c2f292c2c332e281c3b2932382e253138723f3331) or by mail at:

Gundry MD™  
Re: Privacy Compliance Officer  
9465 Wilshire Boulevard, Suite 300  
Beverly Hills, CA, 90212, United States

Effective: 2/28/17
